freegames.net 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - FreeGames.net

**Privacy Policy for FreeGames.net**

The privacy of our visitors to FreeGames.net is important to us. 

At FreeGames.net, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit FreeGames.net, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org. 

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on FreeGames.net to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie:**

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.  
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the[ Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
